toplesscasino.com 2015-03-19

# Topless Casino | Privacy Policy

####  Overview (last updated: January 04, 2015)

1.1 The following describes the information gathering and dissemination practices for the services offered by ToplessCasino (Curacao Regulatory Authority registration number for the purposes of data protection: DP005080).  
1.2 Capitalised terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall be as defined in the General Terms (unless the context otherwise requires). 

2.1 Your personal data (meaning any information about you from which you can be personally identified, such as your name, address, telephone number or email address, and which is referred to in this Privacy Policy as "Your Information"), will be processed by ToplessCasino (including any of its agents and/or employees), and/or our partners and subcontractors in order to be able to provide the full range of the Services to you. Your Information is collected when you register to open an account with us; or when you submit a written query to us.  
2.2 ToplessCasino is is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external websites (operated by parties other than ToplessCasino) that ToplessCasino.com may link to.  
2.3 By using any of the Services, you acknowledge that you have read, and agree to, the terms of this Privacy Policy and that, where you provide us with your Information (including, for the avoidance of doubt, by submitting a query to us through the Website, or where you only partially complete an account registration process), you consent to the use by ToplessCasino (and any partners and subcontractors) of your Information for the purposes set out in paragraph 3 of this Privacy Policy.  
2.4 If you do not wish to provide your Information on the basis set out in this Privacy Policy you should not enter the relevant information in the spaces provided on the relevant part of this Website, or provide any of your information to us over the telephone. However if you do not provide such information, you may not be permitted to make full use of the relevant part of the Services.  
2.5 As part of the account registration process, We also offer visitors registering with us the opportunity to "opt out" from keeping them informed of future events, offers and promotions from ToplessCasino. Visitors who wish to take this option should 'untick' the relevant box in the registration process. you may update your marketing preferences at any time in 'My Account' or by contacting Customer Services. If (where available) you have chosen to receive information on future events, offers and promotions by SMS message to your cellular telephone, you may "opt out" of receiving such information at any time by replying with the word "STOP". To opt out of third party analytics please email us at support@toplesscasino.com and include your device identifier, and once processed, our third party analytics provider will discontinue any analytics on that particular device. 

3.1 ToplessCasino collects your Information in order to:  
3.1.1 Enable us to set up your Account so that you can make full use of all of the features of the Services, including crediting your Account with funds, placing bets and playing games;  
3.1.2 Enable us to receive questions and comments from you through our Online Help Centre, and for us to be able to respond to them;  
3.1.3 Comply with relevant regulations regarding your registration, for example completing age verification checks; and  
3.1.4 (provided that you do not "opt out" from this option), to keep you informed of future events, offers and promotions from ToplessCasino.  
3.2 In addition to the broad purposes identified in paragraph 3.1 above, ToplessCasino will only use your Information, including sharing your Information with our third party partners and subcontractors who process data (including, where appropriate, your Information) on our behalf, for:  
3.2.1 setting up, operating and managing your Account;  
3.2.2 providing any of the Services which are requested of us, and for any proper purpose connected with such provision;  
3.2.3 verifying the accuracy of your Information, including disclosure of such information to third parties (including financial institutions, age verification, and credit reporting agencies) in connection with such purposes (a record of the search will be retained and the third party may use the information to assist other companies for verification purposes);  
3.2.4 preparing statistics relating to the use of the Services by you and other customers;  
3.2.5 preparing and displaying appropriate individualised marketing material and content;  
3.2.6 periodically sending written communications to you to announce important service changes, technical issue updates and changes to the Terms of Use (which includes this Privacy Policy);  
3.2.7 complying with our regulatory duties, obligations and responsibilities under the Curacao Regulatory Authority; and under the relevant legislation and to the relevant regulators in the other jurisdictions where ToplessCasino carries out a regulated activity;  
3.2.8 the investigation of suspected unlawful, fraudulent or other improper activity connected with the Services;  
3.2.9 the reporting of a crime or suspected crime, including money laundering or any fraud; and  
3.2.10 any other purpose which is necessary for the performance of our contractual obligations to you.  
3.3 ToplessCasino will not send you unsolicited information regarding any third party commercial offers or advertisements.  
3.4 ToplessCasino may use your username and/or first name and region for advertising or promotional purposes.  
3.5 Telephone calls to and from our Customer Services Department are recorded for training and security purposes.  
3.6 We may transfer your Information in the event of that we transfer or sell our business or any part of it; including in the event of insolvency.  
3.7 If at any time you wish us to stop processing your Information for the above purposes, then you must contact us and we will take the appropriate steps to stop doing so. Please note that this may mean that your Account will have to be closed. 

4.1 In connection with the provision of Services, ToplessCasino may need to transfer data (including your Information) to:  
4.1.1 our partners and subcontractors. 

5.1 You may update or delete your Information at any time from within your Account through 'My Account/Edit profile' (where available); or by contacting Customer Services.  
5.2 You may obtain a copy of your information held by ToplessCasino by contacting Customer Services. We do require up to twenty-eight (28) days notice to enable us to comply with such a request.
